So, where do you get the glasses with
the tape in the middle?
>> I'd say uh Stanford tradition. Uh I
inherited inherited that tradition, but
you know, we kept it going and um yeah,
just something we thought was cool.
>> Inherited from
>> uh Ben Yuri, so he's on the Vikings now,
but uh he was he was a junior when I
came in as a freshman and then you know,
some guys did back in back in 2013 and
uh you know those Rose Bowl years. You
>> got quite an uh athletic family tree. Uh
you ever met uh Merlin Olsson?
>> Yes sir. So he he passed away when I was
about 6 years old but um yeah you know I
I grew up around him and then you know
my my grandpa is his brother. So we'd
spend a lot of time together. Uh they
grew up in Logan Utah and about 40
minutes away is this place called Bear
Lake and so we we go to Bear Lake all
the time and you know spend time with
both of them and he was a great man and
you know somebody I looked up to in my
football journey.
>> Did you know he was famous and
everything? Uh
>> not when I was six. No he he was humble.
Oh, what about your choice of Stanford?
I know your your dad went to Duke. Was
that a issue in the house?
>> No, it was it was my own decision and
you know my my parents were going to let
me do that and I I fell in love with the
you know rich tight end history at
Stanford and you know those are guys
that I look up to and uh at the time I
was living in San Jose so it was a local
team as well but you know I I really
fell in love with you know the tight end
position early on and um you know wanted
to be the next Zacher, the next Dalton
Schulz, Kobe Parkinson. Do do you have a
sense of how Ben Johnson uses the tight
end group? Obviously Coulson last year,
Cole and then Leaporta and Detroit.
>> Yes, sir. I mean, yeah, Chicago, you
know, we're top five and 12 and 13
personnel usage and obviously it's an
extremely talented tight end room and,
you know, that's something that's going
to get talked about, but you know, I'm
going to come in and I'm going to
compete and, you know, iron sharpens
iron going to make the room better and,
you know, I'm really excited to learn
from those guys. Was that something you
were kind of aware of going when the
Bears called your name or is that since
then kind of diving in on what this team
can do for you?
>> I've I've known that and you know in
this pre-off process watched a lot of
you know a lot of Bears tape and um you
know you got some good tight ends and
you know Coulson Leland text me earlier
today and just kind of welcoming. He's
he's a great guy but you know damn good
football player and that's somebody that
you know I've watched a lot of tape on.
>> What team did you uh what team did you
follow growing up since you're moving
around a lot? Uh I I followed the Rams
growing up. So my my grandpa played for
the Rams for seven years and his brother
uh Merlin Olson Hall of Famer played for
them for about 13 or 14 years. So that
was that was my team growing up but I'm
a Bear now.
>> Did you follow any uh Frank Wek uh you
know being in Nashville?
>> Frank No sir.
>> Okay. Okay. You mentioned your grand was
there last night with you, right?
>> Yes sir.
>> What was it like to share that moment
with him?
>> It was awesome. um you know obviously
you know he he got drafted about you
know 40 50 years ago but you know he was
real happy for me and um it's cool it
runs in the family and you know he's
he's someone that you know I've gotten a
lot of advice from and you know he knows
a thing or two about playing in the
league and you know what it takes and
you know I really respect him and you
know kind of his journey and him helping
me through my journey.
>> Did he tell you how he found out he got
drafted? I'm guessing it wasn't
>> No, it was a little different. My my
grandma actually thought he was getting
drafted to Vietnam. So, it was it was it
was a lot different back then. Um, a
little bit little bit simpler for me,
but yeah, it's a cool story.
>> What kind of advice did he give you?
>> Yeah, I mean, you know, he he stressed
the importance of film. Um, he's he's
big on, you know, step-ups. I don't want
to I don't want this secret to get out
there, but, you know, he's huge on
step-ups and um just kind of developing
your your lateral muscles and your legs.
good for a change of direction and um
you know being able to move laterally is
huge um in football and you know
especially the tight end position where
you got to get good body position to win
and um you know that's something that
I've been doing since I was 15 years old
and you know there's some other stuff
that I won't I won't put out there but
you know he he's been really important
and and you know I think of him a lot in
this moment
>> go ahead that that Vietnam thing was
that like a phone call that he
>> so he he got a call I think he was at
his mom's house and and my grandma,
someone told her that he had gotten
drafted, but she didn't know, she didn't
know what that meant and so she thought
he was going to war. Um, thankfully he
wasn't. But
>> you're come from a football family
obviously, but what would you have done
if you didn't play professionally, but
>> to be honest, I haven't thought much of
that. um you know really thankful for
you know the gifts I've been given and
the ability to play football and you
this has been my dream since I was a
little kid and just so thankful for the
uh you
>> know whether that Stanford degree had
you pointed in some direction.
>> Uh I I majored in computer science that
that was never really the plan. Um uh
but you know I I love my time at
Stanford and um thankful I I was blessed
with amazing coaches and really
appreciative everything that you know
Coach Turner and Coach Bah have done for
me and um you know it's been huge in my
development
>> obviously. Okay, you were one of six
players at the combine to do every
single drill. Why was that important to
you in Indianapolis?
>> Yep. I love to compete. I was telling
coaches all week I was going to do
everything and then I didn't even know
people were going to skip out on stuff
until, you know, right up right up in
towards the end after we did all our
drill work and I was I was like I'm not
going to skip out on the shuttle. So,
you know, obviously um a lot of guys a
lot of guys forego that, but I I just
wanted to get a number on the board and
you know, I knew if I didn't like
anything I could redo it at pro day, but
um yeah, I I wanted to compete and you
know, I get to do it once in my
lifetime, so I felt like I'd take
advantage of it. Being an inline tight
end that embraces the physicality and
the run blocking, it's kind of become a
bit of a specialist position in the
league right now. Were you aware of that
as you kind of went through the
pre-draft process and did it maybe take
your mind to certain teams where that
may be a good fit for you?
>> Yes, sir. Uh blocking is a huge part of
my identity as a player. Um that's
something that I take immense pride in.
that's something that I've, you know,
worked on every day in college and, um,
that's obviously where a lot of my value
is in the league and, uh, you know,
obviously Chicago is a place that's
going to value that. And, um, I'm going
to do everything that I can to, you
know, play my role on this team and, you
know, all I want to do is help the team
be successful and I'm going to do
whatever it takes to make that happen.
>> How much do you embrace and enjoy
playing on special teams?
>> I love playing special teams. So my my
freshman year I played a little bit of
tight end. Um but you know maybe 15
snaps a game in college and uh I played
on every single special team. I think I
had the second most special team snaps
in the country that year and uh that's
something that I really enjoyed and I
wish I got to keep doing it as a senior
obviously um you know you play a lot on
offense. It's tough to play every single
special team but um that's something
that I'm I'm really excited for here. Do
you in some instances probably enjoy or
you miss like that rugby you get?
>> Oh yeah, that's the only time I get to
make tackles. That's the only good
situation I get to make tackles.
>> Did the Bears talk to you about Durham
Spice role or did you watch any of him
uh last season?
>> Yeah. Um yeah, we've talked about it and
uh you know I'm I'm I'm just excited to
be here and uh yeah, going to come in
and compete.
>> Other than tackling people, why do you
enjoy special teams so much? Uh it's
it's a great way to, you know, give back
to the team. Uh the way that it gets
pitched a lot of the time is, you know,
this is the sacrifice that you're making
for the team. You got to go play special
teams, but um you know, I think it's a
great opportunity to go make plays and
especially as a young player, you know,
that's that's how you can kind of make a
name for yourself and carve out a role
on special teams. And especially in the
league, that that's huge. You only get,
you know, what 53 men on a roster,
right? You're going to have to have, you
know, really really good players playing
special teams. And um you know that
that's where I that's where I see myself
is making plays on special teams.
>> You played for a head coach last year,
coached in the NFL.
>> Yes, sir.
>> In what ways do you think that might
help your transition here?
>> Yeah, it's huge. I mean, it's very
similar offense. Um we were in a real
pro style, you know, run first offense
with coach Reich and um love that a lot
of play action. Um I think it'll I think
it'll translate really well. A lot of
the concepts and and plays will be
similar.
>> Coach Johnson was an OC. He was the
tight end's coach. Do you appreciate
playing for a head coach that has a a
background as the tight end's coach or
maybe does it add more pressure because
you know his eyes are constantly on that
position?
>> Absolutely. I mean it it you know means
we're going to get utilized and you know
he's always you know looking for ways to
put us a point of attack and you know
get us the ball and obviously you know
he's a head coach and he's going to do
what's best for the team but you know
that is nice to you know have someone
that's coached the position.
>> Got to your science too.
>> Really? I I did not know that. That was
pretty cool. coaching software.
>> That's That's cool.